[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 2]
What's going on? The test hasn't started yet?
Lu Li hasn't yet come?
[Wu Yang Duke's disciple, Xue]
Look over there.
It's about to start.
All disciples, listen to the order.
Demons have infiltrated the boundary.
Demons?
It's among you.
Within half of an hour,
whoever finds and defeats them
will be deemed to have passed the test.
The test begins now.
What's this?
What's this guy doing?
That's enough.
The test requires only to beat him.
You…
These demons are vicious.
If you do good to him,
you're harming your fellows.
The demon has been removed.
I'm one of the disciples, Xi.
Can I advance to the next level?
Why is the incense still burning?
Is there another demon among us?
Could there be another one? ,
It's not over yet.
Are you the demon?
Stay away from me.
What a trick!
The demon is her.
Me?
If not,
why did the demon have to attack you?
And why did you plead for him?
That's slander.
Cut it out.
I learned such a trick as sprinkling powder
when I was six years old.
Lu Li?
How did you get in?
I have legs, of course I walked in.
I think you were taken as a test question.
So
I didn't come empty-handed.
Here's your chance.
Go and kill him.
No, I'm scared.
You'd better find someone else.
You can't?
I can't.
What are you talking about?
I'm afraid.
You just did a good job. Why can't you do it now?
Hey, look at this.
Oh, I see.
You have the guts to fight with girls.
What you did
just now with the move
is not bad.
Try it.
You're underestimating me.
Wow!
So it's a demon of a tree branch.
Awesome.
That's something.
I accidentally swung and he died?
In fact, what Wu Yang Duke plans to test
is the strong courage to overcome fear
as well as demons.
If you don't have it,
no matter how great you are,
you're not what they want.
Got it?
Welcome to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
This is
the senior female disciple of the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke,
Bai Feng.
[Chief female disciple of the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke, Bai Feng]
We've seen
your performance just now.
Later on, all the disciples who pass this round of tests
will receive a golden flower card
and will be qualified to enter the next round.
I've made it to the second round.
My hand!
My hand.
Brother.
I just saw you fly over in a flash.
Teach me sometime.
100 taels for a pinch. 300 taels for pain.
Brother, I'm Wang Jian. And you?
I'm Lu Li.
Nice to meet you.
Disciples without the golden flower cards
shouldn't be discouraged either.
The Mansion of Wu Yang Duke always welcomes
those who want to fight evil and defend justice.
But only if you have the strength to do so,
not by luck.
Those who pass with the help of others…
It's him.
won't count.
Liu Shao
cheated.
This is the senior male disciple of the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke,
Du Mingchong.
In the past, he was the one
who decided the selection of the disciples.
Senior Du,
do you have other plans here?
Did she get through
with your help?
Senior Du,
I just gave her
some advice.
She managed to do it herself.
You don't deserve
to call me “senior”.
I thought we were peers now that I'm in the Duke's Mansion.
But there's a hierarchy in the Duke's Mansion,
unlike what Wu Yang Duke said
that everyone is equal.
Forgive me for crossing the line.
You're beating around the bush
and pressuring me with what the Lord said.
Then let me see what you can do.
Ouch
Senior Du.
You're the eldest disciple of the mansion.
Why bother with a newcomer like him?
-Besides, the selection process is strict. -Don't move.
-If she doesn't have the talent... -He didn't touch you, did he?
how can she get into the next round?
My ass.
I've already sent out the golden flower card.
Senior Du.
Will you do me a favor?
Since Bai Feng has asked,
-I should do her the favor. -Lu Li, are you okay?
As for whether you can stay in the future,
it depends on their ability.
Liu Shao.
Thank you.
All the disciples who have received their golden flower cards,
please follow me to Yu Yu Hall.
Brother.
What's up?
Do you like Liu Shao?
What are you talking about? Unless I'm blind.
Why does helping her have to mean I like her?
Maybe
she bought me into helping her.
As the old saying goes,
beating is kissing, scolding is loving.
Beating is kissing, scolding is loving?
I'm just kidding.
Look, there's the Yu Yu Hall in front of us.
Let me take you there.
Go.
Let's go.
[Yu Yu Hall]
Kneel.
I've arranged for you to catch Liu Shao.
But only two of you came back alive.
And you came back empty-handed.
How dare you
show up in front of me?
I managed to do it.
It's Lu Sheng's disciple
who ruined it.
Yes, it's Lu Li.
Lu Li was protecting her in secret.
Ao Hen sent you here, right?
Go back and tell that old demon.
I'll take care of Liu Shao.
Tell her to give up.
For so many years,
I've been searching for demon energy
to nourish your young master
and barely keep him alive.
Now
it's a rare chance that Liu Shao shows up
and my son can be cured.
But you two let her get away.
It can't be pardoned.
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Your Majesty!
-In the way of my son's survival. - Forgive me, Your Majesty!
You losers.
How dare you beg for mercy?
Yin, be a good boy.
I promise you.
I will get Liu Shao
and transfer the power from her body to you.
This is Wu Yang Duke.
The lord of the human world?
What an overrated eye candy!
He's useless
except for his good looks.
Can't you see the seat of Wu Yang Duke
is still empty?
I mean…
I mean, how stupid are you?
That's Wu Yang Duke's top general,
Fang Zhan, Chief Fang.
Forget it.
You'll get to know
in the mansion.
Actually,
there's nothing wrong with being overrated eye candy.
Overrated as they are,
they're good-looking anyway.
They look much more pleasing to the eye
than those with an intimidating face.
Happy?
Who is overrated? Who are you talking about?
Be quiet.
Today,
you've come to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
Although you haven't yet become official disciples,
you should know
every disciple of the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
has the responsibility of protecting the human race.
All of you have come here.
I'm sure you all have the desire to eradicate evil
and protect the people.
But to do that,
you will inevitably face risks at all times,
in danger of dying.
If you feel remorse,
you can leave now.
I'll be able to learn something,
so that I don't have to be afraid of Ao Hen.
Good.
If that's the case,
you can settle down in the mansion first.
I'll wait for you to go through hard study
and rigorous trials
to finally succeed
and pacify the demons and protect the beings.
Pacify the demons and protect the beings!
Am I a dog?
Rude.
Come on, follow me.
What?
Don't you understand?
Senior Du was clearly trying to screw you.
Trying to screw me?
You must have offended him in
in some way.
"Survival Guide"?
That's right.
You don't know how to handle people.
You can get in over your head.
Follow the book.
It's the right way.
I've been studying this
for over 20 years.
With this "Survival Guide",
[Survival Guide]
you can make a good living
in the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
[Survival Guide]
[When you see a problem, go around it]
What is this?
Why do I have a similar feeling
of being cheated by you
on the Moon River.
How much is the book?
I can't buy it if it's too expensive.
What are you talking about?
Do we need to talk about money
between us?
Are you kidding?
You're with me, after all.
Anyway, if you don't know what to do,
just read the book.
It explains very clearly.
Let's try to look good
both inside and outside.
Don't be a blockhead.
Okay?
Who's a blockhead? I'm not.
You…
You're not…
Still talking, right?
Give me back my money.
30,000 taels.
Money?
Yes.
Who wants to pay for humiliation?
30,000 taels.
Now.
Actually,
I misspoke.
How can those who make it to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
be a blockhead?
So,
take this as
a token of my appreciation.
Okay?
Brother?
You are 18 years old, and I am 23.
What should you call me?
Brother
Lu Li.
Good girl.
If you want to get along in the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke,
you have to listen to your brother.
Got it?
This liar is not so bad.
There are rules in the mansion.
Male disciples
[Lingxi Yard]
live in Zhulu Yard
[Zhulu Yard]
while female disciples
live in Lingxi Yard.
[Lingxi Yard]
Although the courtyard is large,
don't stroll around.
Male disciples and female disciples
are not allowed to go into each other's courtyard.
Come in, everyone.
This will be your room from now on.
One bed for each of you.
Make the beds.
[Survival Guide]
[Be a good friend and work as much as you can]
Be a good friend.
Work as much as you can.
Does it really work?
Hi, Sister.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Okay.
Let me do it.
No need.
Thank you then.
It's my first time making a quilt.
It feels good.
Miss.
Which bed do I have?
They're all full.
Liu Shao.
You're rich, aren't you?
Find your way.
Then where should I stay?
Come with me.
Come on.
Lu.
What I respect most in my life
is a wise and brave man like you.
Don't crowd inside the small room with other disciples.
You can stay with me.
Look, take your pick.
Take your pick.
Wait.
The Mansion of Wu Yang Duke has always been fair.
Why are you being special?
You're even given a room
that only the official disciples can stay in?
Actually,
my grandfather
did great things with the former Wu Yang Duke.
He was a meritorious minister.
He begged the Lord
to take care of me.
Good for you. Offspring of a meritorious minister.
Should I
seek shelter from you then?
Not really.
I only get a little help with food and supplies.
As for the following test,
we have to fight it with our ability.
I am
stupid and fat,
and slow to learn martial arts.
No one in my clan thinks highly of me.
Even my father is laughed at for this.
So your father…
Is he
disappointed in you?
No.
My father said I was the best.
My father told me
when I finished my studies,
he'd celebrate it with a banquet
and arrange a marriage for me.
You must come then.
We can have some drinks.
This way.
This is my bed.
You can sleep here from now on.
Oh.
I'll clean it up for you.
There is no other choice.
I'll have to ask you to crowd inside the room with me.
It's okay.
It's fine here.
But Sister,
why do you live here too?
You mean why I live in such a humble place, right?
Actually,
I'm just a lowly servant of the Duke's Mansion.
I do menial work with Bai.
And I've been doing it for a long time.
So I'm allowed to take care of the newcomers.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
There's food and shelter here.
I'm fully clothed every day.
I'm satisfied.
By the way,
you haven't gotten your disciple's uniform yet, have you?
I have a suit here.
You can wear it for now.
New uniforms will be brought tomorrow.
Thank you, Sister.
What does the "Survival Guide" say?
Money can make the Devil work for you.
There is nothing money can't do.
If someone treats you well,
you have to repay him with money.
Sister, this is for you.
Did someone teach you to take care of things with money?
Then you're using it on the wrong person.
I'm just an insignificant person.
You'd better think about
how to pass the following tests
with your competence.
Oh.
What Brother Lu Li?
He's just a liar.
Damn liar.
I was blind
to think he was immortal.
He doesn't look anything like that.
He's just
a big shithead.
[Chief of the Human Race, Wu Yang Duke]
Who is it?
Sir.
Your sword dance was spectacular.
You just... swish, swish.
Swish, swish.
Awesome.
My father told me
a good show
must be rewarded.
Do you think I'm an entertainer?
That's not the same.
Sir, don't be embarrassed.
Take it.
It's a small token of my appreciation.
The one outside, come out.
Lu Li?
Sir, you don't have to be polite to me.
You're not dressed like
the low-ranking disciples, like me,
nor are you dressed like high-ranking disciples, like Du Mingchong.
I suppose
you're just a lowly disciple.
And you're old.
It must be hard for you.
Am I right, Lu Li?
I don't know you.
I'm Liu Shao.
I'm disciple Lu Li.
This is one of the newcomers, Liu Shao.
Greetings, Wu Yang Duke.
My lord,
please forgive Liu Shao's ignorance.
Kneel.
You...
You are Wu Yang Duke?
No.
She... she...
I'm just an old
and lowly disciple.
It's hard for me.
No, no.
I... I was wrong.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
In the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke,
who else would wear neither the high-ranking disciple's uniform
nor the low-ranking disciple's uniform?
I didn't know that.
Besides,
no matter how ignorant you are,
you must have heard of
the Lord's Lightning Slash, right?
Lighting Slash?
That was Lightning Slash you just did?
Do you think
it's worthy of your gold leaf?
It's much more valuable than the gold leaf.
Can you teach me?
Well, you...
Do you really want to learn?
Yes.
This is the simplest move of the Lighting Slash.
Learn it.
My Lord, can you slow down a bit?
It was too fast, and I didn't catch it.
Shut up.
My Lord,
she is stupid and ignorant.
How can she learn your Lightning Slash?
Please forgive her.
She knows she's wrong.
Do you think I'm joking?
I know who you are.
The demons out there are all after her.
As for you,
the day you came to the mansion, you fought the demons alone.
You were lucky enough to defeat Ao Hen.
You are not simple characters.
My Lord.
You must be mistaken.
I... I...
I have a task for you now.
The official test is half a month away.
If she doesn't learn this move,
the two of you will have to leave the Duke's Mansion together.
You'll also be charged with
the crime of disrespect.
Do I have a grudge against you?
Do I owe you a lot of money?
Why did you come to this forest?
What?
You don't have a grudge against me.
But you owe me a lot of money.
You took my money
and left me alone.
So I ran to the forest
to curse you.
How do you know I don't care about you?
Did you ever take care of me?
I didn't?
I…
What kind of crap is the "Survival Guide"
you gave me?
It was a lie.
I almost didn't even have a place to live.
And
you knew I was new at the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
I didn't know the place well.
But you didn't even come to see me.
I mean.
Aren't you good at martial arts?
I'm just
a useless liar.
How can you
take what a girl says in anger seriously?
Oh, I…
Oh, okay, okay.
I'm wrong, all right?
You are wrong.
I'm wrong.
Give me your hand.
What?
Give it to me.
I'll show you the other world of the liar.
Close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
[Dream Moon Boundary]
What a beautiful place!
Where is this place?
This is the illusion I created with my magic,
Dream Moon Boundary.
But you can't use illusions inside the mansion.
My master taught me how to create
the Dream Moon Boundary.
It's different from other illusions.
It won't be discovered.
Oh.
Pull it out.
I was thinking about
what weapon you should use.
The Lord happened to ask you to practice the Lighting Slash.
How about
trying this sword?
It should suit you well.
It seems
that you've been helping me out.
I'll give you an extra 5,000 taels.
Let's wait until you learn the Lighting Slash.
But
there's half a month left.
I'm suspicious about if I can do it.
You don't know.
In fact, time inside the illusion
passes by much more slowly than outside.
But now,
it's not a matter of time.
We need to know the sword technique of Lighting Slash before carrying on.
We don't have the sword manual.
Now our fate is in your hands.
You have to learn the Lighting Slash.
Or else
we'll be crushed to pieces
like the gold leaf just now.
As for things I'm interested in,
like swordplay,
drawing charms, and skits,
I'm quick to learn them.
But not the things like poetry, rituals, and music,
because I don't like them.
Don't worry, I'll teach you.
Okay.
The first step,
we can't let the little flame
fall from the tip of the sword.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Come on.
Concentrate on
the spirit fire at the tip of the sword.
The sword follows the mind. The mind follows the heart. The mind and the heart coexist.
The power of the sword
will naturally be formed.
[Mansion of Wu Yang Duke]
The new disciples' martial arts test
is in a few days.
Before the test,
according to the Lord's instructions,
I will teach you to practice
the Duke's Mansion's unique method of mental discipline
-to improve your cultivation. -Brother.
You've been hanging out with Liu Shao for the past several days.
Is there something you're not telling me?
Nonsense.
I'm afraid she'll be eliminated. I was tutoring her.
You're not worried about me being eliminated?
I can't believe the new disciple, Liu Shao,
wanted to learn the Lighting Slash.
I gave her half a month's time.
Do you think
she can learn it?
Well.
I think you've overestimated her.
She may not be able to learn it
even in a year.
How much can she learn
in half a month?
I've been practicing for so long.
Do you think I've accomplished it?
The stance is 70 percent like it.
Breath, 30 percent.
Sword intent…
Not a single bit.
What is the sword intent of Lighting Slash?
I have a three-foot blade
to eradicate all the unjust things.
This is the sword intent of the Lighting Slash.
Back in the day,
there was a time
when Wu Yang Duke did great things.
What injustice?
Of course.
This is
too complicated
for Miss Liu
who is high and mighty
and spends money at will,
having no idea of what the world's suffering is.
I don't know about the world's suffering?
I was being chased
by Ao Hen and had no place to stay before I came here.
Demons, big or small,
always come after me.
And now,
I could be killed by Wu Yang Duke at any time.
I'd like to be the old Miss Liu again.
But now
I can't even go home.
Um.
Actually,
it's not that bad.
Don't worry.
I have your back.
I will make your family reunite.
Trust me.
Come on.
Keep practicing.
I should think Ao Hen as an injustice.
Kill her, kill her.
She has gone a little crazy with her practice.
I have to be careful when we practice today.
Your stance is not right.
Who taught you that?
Kill her!
Liu Shao hit Du.
With what?
I don't know.
A golden light.
Liu has been hiding her strength.
Are you okay, Du?
That's all for today's practice.
Everyone, go back to your rooms
and prepare for tomorrow's test.
Amazing.
I can easily exceed the time limit
practicing in the Dream Moon Boundary.
I can't let others find out.
What are you eating? Are you sick?
No, I'm not.
What's wrong?
Sit down.
What's this?
Give it to me.
Spirit-locking pill?
This is Xi's.
Why did she give you this?
Why did you eat it?
Tell me.
Today I went to beg Bai Feng.
She exceptionally let me take the disciple test too.
But I didn't expect such a coincidence.
I was assigned to a group with Xi.
But why would she harm you?
I've worked in the mansion for many years
and learned a lot of skills secretly.
Xi might
be afraid to lose to me
and lose face if I eliminate her.
No way.
I have to go to tell Bai Feng.
Don't go.
Why?
My mother is working as a cook in Xi's mansion.
She signed a life-and-death contract.
So Liu Shao,
it's okay.
Forget it.
Forget it? Why forget it?
We can't just let it go.
Let's see.
This is the sentence.
Xi.
-How dare you poison Xue? -Take a good look.
Liu Shao, are you crazy?
At tomorrow's disciple test,
we will fight against each other.
The losers will quit.
You're afraid of losing to Xue, so you poisoned her.
What are you talking about?
This is slander.
This is evidence.
This is your medicine bottle.
It still smells like the spirit-locking pill.
You're a fool.
Your evidence is gone.
I'll go tell Bai Feng.
Fine by me.
Xue just gets sick.
Go and tell on me.
See if the lowly cook's daughter
dares to fight against me.
Burn the fire, cook the food.
She's self-reliant.
Who are you to say she's lowly?
A lowly person is born to be inferior.
Miss Liu,
don't pretend to be noble.
We're the same.
We were born to be waited on.
We're not the same.
We've never been the same.
Tomorrow,
I will challenge you
for Xue.